{
    "subject": "resource/House_at_1487_Loma_Vista_Street",
    "predicate": "ontology/yearOfConstruction",
    "object": "1913",
    "human_readable": "House at 1487 Loma Vista Street was constructed in 1913.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9776248931884766,
            "question": "When was the House at 1487 Loma Vista Street built?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9580016136169434,
            "question": "In what year did construction on the house at 1487 Loma Vista Street begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9373080730438232,
            "question": "What was the purpose of constructing the House at 1487 Loma Vista Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8913348317146301,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about the architectural style of the House at 1487 Loma Vista Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8359074592590332,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about the history of the House at 1487 Loma Vista Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8221681714057922,
            "question": "Were there any notable events that happened in the House at 1487 Loma Vista Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8032622933387756,
            "question": "What is the address of the house that was constructed in 1913?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7707123160362244,
            "question": "How old is the House at 1487 Loma Vista Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25939077138900757,
            "question": "Where is the house located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22861340641975403,
            "question": "Is there a specific year associated with the construction of the house at this address?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=House at 1487 Loma Vista Street was constructed in 1913.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3113_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is the house located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3113_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is the House at 1487 Loma Vista Street?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3113_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the address of the house that was constructed in 1913?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3113_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3113_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The text mentions that \"Built in 1913 in the Pasadena Heights Tract, the architect and builder of the house at 1487 Loma Vista Street are unknown.\" This implies that the house at 1487 Loma Vista Street was indeed constructed in 1913."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe statement \"House at 1487 Loma Vista Street was constructed in 1913\" is supported by the document information, which states that \"Built in 1913 in the Pasadena Heights Tract, the house at 1487 Loma Vista Street...\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}